playpartyplan.com 2019-01-02

# Privacy Policy - Play Party Plan

Play Party Plan, [https://www.playpartyplan.com](https://www.playpartyplan.com/)/ (“Website”) uses the following privacy policy (“Privacy Policy”).

We respect your privacy and are committed to protecting it. The purpose of this Privacy Policy is to inform you what personally identifiable data we may collect and how it might be used. This privacy policy only applies to this website.

### WHAT INFORMATION DO WE COLLECT AND HOW IS IT USED?

 **Information You Voluntarily Submit to the Website** : We may collect personal information from you such as your name or email address when you voluntarily provide it by leaving a comment, subscribing to an email newsletter, or submitting a contact form.

 **Automatically-Collected Information** : We automatically collect certain information about you and the device with which you access the Website. For example, when you use the Website, we will log your IP address, operating system type, browser type, referring website, pages you viewed, and the dates/times when you accessed the Website. We may also collect information about actions you take when using the Website, such as links clicked.

 **Cookies** : We may log information using cookies, which are small data files stored on your browser by the Website. We may use both session cookies, which expire when you close your browser, and persistent cookies, which stay on your browser until deleted, to provide you with a more personalized experience on the Website. [Read more about our cookie policy and how to adjust your cookie settings here](https://www.playpartyplan.com/cookie-policy/).

### HOW YOUR INFORMATION MAY BE USED

We may use the information collected in the following ways:

  * To operate and maintain the Website;
  * To send you promotional information, such as newsletters that include an unsubscribe link.
  * To send you administrative communications, such as administrative emails, confirmation emails, technical notices, updates on policies, or security alerts;
  * To respond to your comments;
  * To provide you with user support;
  * To track and measure advertising on the Website;
  * To protect, investigate, and deter against unauthorized or illegal activity.

### THIRD-PARTY USE OF PERSONAL INFORMATION

We may share your information with third parties when you explicitly authorize us to share your information.

Each third-party service provider’s use of your personal information is dictated by their respective privacy policies.

The Website currently uses the following third-party service providers:

 **Google Analytics** – this service tracks Website usage and provides information such as referring websites and user actions on the Website. Google Analytics may capture your IP address, but no other personal information is captured by Google Analytics.

 **Mailerlite** – this service is used for delivery of email updates and newsletters. We store your name and email address for purposes of delivering such communications.  Please refer to [Mailerlite’s privacy policy](https://www.mailerlite.com/privacy-policy) for further information.

 **PushCrew** – this service is used to send you push notifications through your web browser, should you choose.  Please refer to [PushCrew’s privacy policy](https://pushcrew.com/privacy-policy/) for further information.

At this time, your personal information is not shared with any other third-party applications. This list may be amended from time to time in the Website’s sole discretion.

Except when required by law, we will not sell, distribute, or reveal your email addresses or other personal information without your consent; however, we may disclose or transfer personal information collected through the Website to third parties if we sell this business.

### ANONYMOUS DATA

From time to time, we may use anonymous data, which does not identify you alone, or when combined with data from other parties. This type of anonymous data may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses. Examples of this anonymous data may include analytics or information collected from cookies.

### PUBLICLY VISIBLE INFORMATION

If you leave a comment, certain information may be publicly visible.  Your email address will never be available publicly.  At your option, you may also add a profile description, and a link to your website.

Users may see your username, profile description and website information.

### COOKIES

The Website uses cookies to store visitors’ preferences, record user-specific information on what pages users access or visit, ensure that visitors are not repeatedly sent the same banner ads, customize Website content based on visitors’ browser type or other information that the visitor sends. Cookies may also be used by third-party services, such as Google Analytics, as described herein.

[Read more about our cookie policy and how to adjust your cookie settings here](https://www.playpartyplan.com/cookie-policy/).

### ADVERTISING

 **Display Ads**

We may use third-party advertising companies to serve content and advertisements when you visit the Website, which may use cookies, as noted above.

 **Retargeting  Ads**

From time to time, the Website may engage in remarketing efforts with third-party companies, such as Google, Facebook, or Instagram, in order to market the Website. These companies use cookies to serve ads based on someone’s past visits to the Website.

 **Affiliate Program Participation**

The Website may engage in affiliate marketing, which is done by embedding tracking links into the Website. If you click on a link for an affiliate partnership, a cookie will be placed on your browser to track any sales for purposes of commissions.

Play Party Plan is a participant in the Amazon Services LLC Associates Program, an affiliate advertising program designed to provide a means for sites to earn advertising fees by advertising and links to Amazon.com.  As part of this Amazon Associates program, the Website will post customized links, provided by Amazon, to track the referrals to their website. This program utilizes cookies to track visits for the purposes of assigning commission on these sales.

 **Newsletters**

On the Website, you may subscribe to our newsletter via Mailerlite, which may be used for advertising purposes. All newsletters sent may contain tracking pixels. The pixel is embedded in emails and allows an analysis of the success of online marketing campaigns. Because of these tracking pixels, we may see if and when you open an email and which links within the email you click. Also, this allows the Website to adapt the content of future newsletters to the interests of the user. This behavior will not be passed on to third parties.

### RIGHTS RELATED TO YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION

 **Opt-out** – You may opt-out of future email communications by following the unsubscribe links in our emails. You may also notify us at britni@playpartyplan.com to be removed from our mailing list.

 **Access** – You may access the personal information we have about you by submitting a request to britni@playpartyplan.com.

 **Amend** – You may contact us at britni@playpartyplan.com to amend or update your personal information.

 **Forget** – You may request that we erase or forget your personal data. To do so, please submit a request to britni@playpartyplan.com.

Please note that we may need to retain certain information for record keeping purposes or to complete transactions, or when required by law.

### SENSITIVE PERSONAL INFORMATION

At no time should you submit sensitive personal information to the Website. This includes your social security number, information regarding race or ethnic origin, political opinions, religious beliefs, health information, criminal background, or trade union memberships. If you elect to submit such information to us, it will be subject to this Privacy Policy.

### CHILDREN’S INFORMATION

The Website does not knowingly collect any personally identifiable information from children under the age of 16. If a parent or guardian believes that the Website has personally identifiable information of a child under the age of 16 in its database, please contact us at britni@playpartyplan.com and we will remove such information from our records.

CONTACT INFORMATION

At any time, please contact us at britni@playpartyplan.com for questions related to this Privacy Policy.

Last updated: May 25, 2018.
